Lauren Chun

laurenmchun111@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/laurenmchun

Data Analyst

Using technology, research, and designs, I apply my blend of quantitative research skills and creative design expertise within a forward-thinking organization, where I can contribute to innovative projects while advancing my knowledge in emerging technologies.

Education

New York University, Master of Professional Studies Design and Technology Program (ITP)
San Jose State University, Bachelor of Fine Arts Digital Media Art

May 2023 May 2021

Technical Skills

Technical – SQL, Python, Excel, Google Sheets, HTML5 CSS3, Javascript, Node.js, APIs, React, Front End Development, Express, ARIA, Looker, Tableau, Big Query, dbt, Airflow, A/B Testing, research methodologies, results analysis, MV testing

Organization - Google Suite, Jira, Asana, Microsoft Office, Google Sheets, Agile

Professional Experience

A/P/A Institute, New York, NY

Mar 2023 - Jan 2024

UX Engineer, Freelance

- Identified key features and needs of users and stakeholders. Articulated design decisions and drive stakeholder alignment.
- Developed and deployed web application for responsive design in desktop, mobile, and iframe.
- Analyzed and monitored website's user activity with google analytics to find insight to improve user experience through site..

Samsung Research America, Santa Clara, CA

May 2022 - Dec 2022

Metaverse UX Researcher & Designer, Intern

- Designed end-to-end hi-fidelity mixed reality prototypes for tools in Unity in collaboration with PMs,engineers, and tech artists.
- Led research of segment specific uses of potential new technologies for use cases to showcase innovative solutions to stakeholders and potential customers.
- Leveraged user-centered design principles and conducted extensive user research. Created an intuitive and visually appealing menu interface, facilitating easy navigation through application.

New York University, New York, NY

April 2022 - May 2022

UX Researcher Graduate Assistant

- Conducted in-depth qualitative research studies, including user interviews, card sorts and other research methodologies to gather valuable insights into user behaviors, needs, and pain points.
- Assisted in the design and execution of user testing sessions, employing usability testing methodologies to evaluate interface designs and gather feedback for iterative improvement.
- Analyzed qualitative data using Excel, synthesizing findings into actionable recommendations to inform product design decisions and enhance user satisfaction.

San Jose State University ECampus, San Jose, CA

Aug 2019 - Dec 2019

UI/UX Research/Design Intern

- Redesigned UI for student experience in physical chemistry class, resulting in 84% of students indicating easier understanding of concepts.
- Designed and developed for iOS and Android mobile applications, ensuring seamless user interactions and optimizing the UX within the VR educational environment.